{
    "subject": "resource/Friedrich_Hayek",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Austria-Hungary",
    "human_readable": "Friedrich Hayek was born in Austria-Hungary.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.945165753364563,
            "question": "Was Friedrich Hayek Austrian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8682368397712708,
            "question": "Where was Friedrich Hayek born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7596238851547241,
            "question": "In what year was Friedrich Hayek born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5666486024856567,
            "question": "What country was Austria-Hungary?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5610993504524231,
            "question": "What is Friedrich Hayek known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4974079430103302,
            "question": "Where did Friedrich Hayek work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30285656452178955,
            "question": "What were Friedrich Hayek's main ideas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2811902165412903,
            "question": "Who influenced Friedrich Hayek's thinking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21112100780010223,
            "question": "Did Friedrich Hayek receive any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1939319223165512,
            "question": "What is the name of Friedrich Hayek's famous book?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Friedrich Hayek was born in Austria-Hungary.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7783_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Friedrich Hayek receive any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7783_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who influenced Friedrich Hayek's thinking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7783_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were Friedrich Hayek's main ideas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7783_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7783_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as multiple sources (files 8.txt and 6.txt) confirm that Friedrich Hayek was indeed born in Austria-Hungary."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the provided documents, which state that Friedrich Hayek was born in Vienna, Austria-Hungary. Therefore, the statement \"Friedrich Hayek was born in Austria-Hungary\" is supported by the context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}